SHIRLEY KAFFREY

Loveland, CO | C: 719-238-9967 | Shirley.Kaffrey@gmail.com

Summary

Web Developer knowledgeable in React, javascript, node.js and CSS. I have a stellar customer service record and superb work ethic. Prior work experience in Healthcare as a manager, meeting productivity standards and interpersonal communication. I strive to be a part of a team that provides quality client support in a culture of innovation, collaboration and technical advancement.

Skills

- React, Javascript and node.js
- Creative Problem Solver
- Attention to Details

- Adept at communicating efficiently and effectively
- Learning C++

Portfolio, Profile, GitHub

- https://shirleyk.herokuapp.com/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shirley-k-59835b158/
- https://github.com/Sjazfrey

Experience

Software Developer Internship Queen's Web

01/2021 to present Remote

Frontend React developer who's responsibilities includes implementing designs to create an Enterprise level application similar to Groupon.

Software Developer Student General Assembly

05/2020 to 08/2020 Remote

Software Engineering Immersive Program:

Applied skills in CRUD apps, GitHub, DOM manipulation, AJAX, NodeJS, HTML, React, Javascript, CSS, jQuery, Express, 7 RESTful routes, MongoDB and Mongoose, Group Project, Sessions and Authentication, along with Heroku. Developed 4 projects utilizing the above mentioned skills and technologies.

Rehab Director / Physical Therapist Assistant Legacy Healthcare

04/2014 to 03/2020 Longmont, Colorado

- As Rehab Director my responsibilities include directing the growth and development of the rehab program, performing tasks to meet the fiscal budget required, ordering supplies necessary for the function of the therapy department and maintaining professional working relations with the patients, building management and vendors. Responsibilities also included requesting orders from physicians and verifying insurance benefits, along with performing patient care.
- Additionally, as a Physical Therapist Assistant I am proficient in all competency areas including patient care, communication with the Physical Therapist, program development, documentation, therapy software responsibilities and patient rights and safety.

Education and Training

Software Developer
General Assembly
Remote

Associate of Applied Science: Physical Therapy

Colby Community College

Certifications

Level 1 Dementia Management Certificate